<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raw Thoughts</title>
    <description>Raw thoughts that keep hovering over Anurag Aryan's head.</description>
    <link>http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 17:23:01 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 17:23:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding my voice</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;raw-thoughts-blog-number-two&quot;&gt;Raw Thoughts blog number two.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been on Quora and tried being intellectual, and on twitter trying to
show my funny side, faked on facebook my real self, on reddit being the
silent observer and within the stackoverflow community acting as know 
it all, nothing worked.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not one of those who smoke half a quart of marijuana and a six-pack
but I know one who does, I don’t study from day in and day ut but I know
one of that kind, I’m not courageous enough to drop out of college to 
persue my dream but there have been people who have dared to do so, I don’t
go gymming daily, bulking up and gaining muscles but some people I like does,
I can never be a Casanova with ladies but been with such personalities for
long enough to learn all the moves. So my vice is a borrowed one, I may not
be interesting enough for you but have lived stories of enough people to 
interest you. I tell tales of people you may know, at least I does.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 16:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/finding-my-voice.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/finding-my-voice.html</guid>
        
        <category>my voice, tales, people, personalities</category>
        
        
        <category>life, thoughts</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World.</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;raw-thoughts-blog-number-one&quot;&gt;Raw Thoughts blog number One.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not a writer nor your traditional a post a week blogger. Don’t expect 
anything from this blog or you’ll be disappointed. This is just going to be 
the dumping zone for my brain’s musing.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few things I’ve learned in my travels through this crazy college life which 
is about to end.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One&lt;/strong&gt;, A morning of awkwardness is better than a night of loneliness.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;, You’ve your whole life to make sensible and mature decisions, 
this is not the time.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three&lt;/strong&gt;, GPA is not important, except during placements, approaching 
teachers for project, asking class nerds for favors, or to deserve respect 
from juniors.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Four&lt;/strong&gt;, You’re never going to remember the 8am class in the morning. 
What you’re going to remember is the 9am screw up you did 
between the 8am &amp;amp; 10am class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Five&lt;/strong&gt;, Go talk to her asshole, she won’t kill you and anyway at this 
stage there’ll be no heartbreak that alcohol won’t fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I wrap this up, I want to ask why is this country of Engineers 
producing sub-par engineers working in a call centre?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2015 16:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/hello-world.html</guid>
        
        <category>college, engineers</category>
        
        
        <category>college</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
