<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raw Thoughts</title>
    <description>Raw thoughts that keep hovering over Anurag Aryan's head.</description>
    <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2015 14:08:52 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2015 14:08:52 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why I love Classic Rock.</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-beatles&quot;&gt;The Beatles&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From The Beatles I learned how to live in peace and harmony with other people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;led-zeppelin&quot;&gt;Led Zeppelin&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Led Zeppelin I learned what love actually means&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;jimi-hendrix&quot;&gt;Jimi Hendrix&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Jimi Hendrix I understood what happiness and beauty mean&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bob-dylan&quot;&gt;Bob Dylan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Bob Dylan I learned that it’s okay to change yourself with time and say what you want to say even when you’re expected to say different&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;black-sabbath-and-dio&quot;&gt;Black Sabbath and Dio&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Black Sabbath and Dio I learned that I should appreciate sadness, because it makes us real&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;metallica-and-megadeth&quot;&gt;Metallica and Megadeth&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Metallic and Megadeth I understood the suffering of others and how I should do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;queen&quot;&gt;Queen&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And of course, from Queen I understood that hurting others will make me suffer too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nirvana&quot;&gt;Nirvana&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From Nirvana I understood that pleasure comes from me, so I should find things that I enjoy, not conform to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deep-purple-and-rainbow&quot;&gt;Deep Purple and Rainbow&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and well,Deep Purple and Rainbow are one of thee things that I enjoy because they make real, genius music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;all-this-has-now-made-me-into-the-person-i-am-today-and-honestly-i-appreciate-it&quot;&gt;All this has now made me into the person I am today, and honestly, I appreciate it.&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/why-i-love-classic-rock.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/why-i-love-classic-rock.html</guid>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Isolated Vocal Tracks</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are 11 of my favorite isolated vocal tracks on YouTube. These are in no particular order but every one of them has a potential to send a shiver down your spine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nirvana--smells-like-teen-spirit&quot;&gt;Nirvana – ‘Smells Like Teen Spirit’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/GmUR7sjcuzQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nirvana--territorial-pissing&quot;&gt;Nirvana – ‘Territorial Pissing’&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/DjZCpidgKM8&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;eminem--lose-yourself&quot;&gt;Eminem – ‘Lose Yourself’&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/T8a-4WOaBK4&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-beatles--dont-let-me-down&quot;&gt;The Beatles – ‘Don’t Let Me Down’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/X_1b0nZONes&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;queen-and-david-bowie-under-pressure&quot;&gt;Queen and David Bowie ‘Under Pressure’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/uMQb9LCNGxs&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;radiohead--creep&quot;&gt;Radiohead – ‘Creep’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/gNCx8Ij02ls&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adele--rolling-in-the-deep&quot;&gt;Adele – ‘Rolling In The Deep’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/n84uLQanjBg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-white-stripes--seven-nation-army&quot;&gt;The White Stripes – ‘Seven Nation Army’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/t5nZ2fm8kTM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;paul-mccartney--maybe-im-amazed&quot;&gt;Paul McCartney – ‘Maybe I’m Amazed’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/WeeNPLh2_qQ&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-rolling-stones--gimme-shelter&quot;&gt;The Rolling Stones – ‘Gimme Shelter’&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/y5rUKbI3Y-M&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pearl-jam--black&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam – Black&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/pfQnUI3AGO8&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the playlist of all the above videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/videoseries?list=PLMlT0xC0Elny4PJ5_LluAOtXowaBfZU9h&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to download this playlist or any other playlist for that matter, you can check out this video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; src=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/embed/AmL5aKMkCnk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot;&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/isolated-vocal-tracks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/isolated-vocal-tracks.html</guid>
        
        <category>vocal tracks</category>
        
        <category>music</category>
        
        <category>nirvana</category>
        
        <category>eminem</category>
        
        <category>the beatles</category>
        
        <category>queen</category>
        
        <category>david bowie</category>
        
        <category>radiohead</category>
        
        <category>adele</category>
        
        <category>the white stripes</category>
        
        <category>the rolling stones</category>
        
        <category>pearl jam</category>
        
        
        <category>music</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>21 to millions</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“So what have you decided? You’re going to tell your Dad about it?” I asked Sushant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 25th of April, 2010. We were sitting at a bar in Delhi and Sushant was gulping glasses of beer at a go. Today IPL 2010 came to the end with Chennai Super Kings wining over Mumbai Indians in a much unexpected match and leaving Sushant out of 50 thousand bucks with which he was supposed to pay the hostel fee. Those days betting on IPL matches was the “in-thing” at boy’s hostels. Everyone had their bet but some people took it a little too far, so as to lose a hefty sum of money. 50k is quite a sum for a college guy. But like always Sushant’s face hasn’t lost its calmness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Dad doesn’t need to know about my loss, I’ll earn my money back.” he said with a smirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Do you even have any idea what you are talking about?” At the moment I was much more tensed than he seemed to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had known Sushant all my life. we went to same high school at Patna and finally took admission in the same college, GIT Delhi. He was a true trouble magnet. I can’t tell of a single year in his life which had passed by without one or two big issues. So there we were drinking beer; with him in deep shit, smiling with a supposedly weird solution in his head and me worried about him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Have you heard about the poker group in M block? I’ll play with them and earn my hostel fee back.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Aren’t you missing the most important thing?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nah! I’ve got everything fixed.  I have got a jack to their group and we are playing tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But you don’t know how to play Blackjack you jackass. And what about the initial money you require, have you got any money?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Ah! I thought you’ll ask that, I’ve read everything about Blackjack a.k.a 21. It’s just maths and you know I’ve a gifted mind for maths.”he said with a wink,”and as far as money is concerned that’s where you come to play. You’re lending me 1 thousand bucks for tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Dude you serious? You never even asked me, what if I say no?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“you are my bro, I know you like I know my weeds or even better. You’ve got the money and you’re giving me tonight.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Just don’t lose my money.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 5 am when I received Sushant’s call the next day, even before I could say hello in my half asleep mode a sound came over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Dude this blackjack is awesome. I’m coming to your room and yeah I’ve made 10k last night.” he screamed in his usual happy voice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“yeah, come over.”, I said and slept again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was 9 in the monday morning and we were sitting at the hostel’s mess having our breakfast. Sushant was describing every itsy bitsy detail of the last night and how his love for maths has grown even more after his win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So you’re sure you’re not going to get addicted to this.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Nah! I’ll only play until I win my 50k back.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Good luck with that. I’m not sure about blackjack replacing betting as your addiction.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Don’t act like my mommy.”, he grumbled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After few sessions with M block guys, he won all the money he required and even some more. He promised me that he won’t be playing with them again but he had to do something with his recently acquired skill. He was not the kind of guy to sit idle. Finally he decided to make an blackjack application for android platform. Being a student of Computer Engineer, it was not hard for him to design the basic layout for the game. But what would have made his game exclusive was the main concern. After 2-3 weeks he came to my room with 3 pages scribbled with numbers and letters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What’s this?”, I asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This is the algorithm for my game, and it will make my new game ’21 to millions’ famous.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A weird name you’ve thought of.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Just like me. people start playing game 21 and get to win million. smart eh?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“very.”, I smiled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only in few weeks the download count of the app increased to thousand. It was free and even after so much fame he decided it to leave free, he was different.  After few months a recent engineering graduate from a college in Boston contacted him to talk about his game and his interest in software development. After few chatting session and mutual interest at the same thing they decided to co-found a software development company once Sushant completes his degree in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same bar we started but the year rolled to 2013. He was too lost in his thought to answer my question at first. I shook him to ask again, “So what have you decided? You’re going to tell your Dad about it?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I guess so, but can’t tell him on the phone, it’s THE face news. They’re our first sponsor and they’re funding us half a million dollars. So I’ve to get to New York by April 15th.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/21-to-millions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/21-to-millions.html</guid>
        
        <category>21</category>
        
        <category>Sushant</category>
        
        <category>IPL</category>
        
        <category>college</category>
        
        <category>mobile app</category>
        
        
        <category>fiction</category>
        
        <category>story</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To kill a Mockingbird by Harper Lee</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;margin: 10px; float: left&quot; alt=&quot;Book Cover&quot; src=&quot;http://i0.wp.com/i1326.photobucket.com/albums/u643/BeerSting/Book%20covers/to-kill-a-mockingbird-400x400-imadat2amn7wzuqv_zps9657b0e7.jpeg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Title: To Kill a Mockingbird&lt;br /&gt;
Author: Harper Lee&lt;br /&gt;
Publisher: Random House (2010)&lt;br /&gt;
ISBN: 9780099549482&lt;br /&gt;
Genre: Classics / Historical Fiction&lt;br /&gt;
Pages: 320&lt;br /&gt;
Source: Personal Copy&lt;br /&gt;
Rating: 5/5  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some books are just good as books. They are well-written piece with creative imaginary and the author making sure that the book entertains you. But you can’t confine the books like To Kill a Mockingbird in these boundaries. The book has all those quality along with the important messages dealing with racism and our social scenario which has impacted many people over the last five decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a story about Scout and her older brother Jem‘s childhood in Alabama and how a series of events shook their innocence, shaped their character and taught them about human nature. The book is basically divided into two parts. The first part revolves around the narrator, a six-year-old girl named Scout, her older brother Jem and their friend Dill, from Mississippi, who visits Maycomb and stays with his aunt Rachel every summer. Scout describes the city as, “Maycomb was an old town, but it was a tired old town when I first knew it.” So they didn’t have much to do whole summer other than playing and wondering about the mysterious figure, Boo Radley. The Radleys were the “weird family” of town and had lots of rumor about them, and since no one had ever seen Boo Radley, the trio always wanted him to come out of his house across the street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“They are certainly entitled to think that, and they’re entitled to full respect for their opinions, but before I can live with other folks, i have got to live with myself. The one thing that doesn’t abide by the majority rule is a person’s conscience”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;-&lt;em&gt;Atticus Finch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second part of the novel follows Scout and Jem as they deal with the repercussions of their father’s court case. Atticus Finch is a lawyer who is representing an innocent black man, Tom Robinson, accused of raping the town drunk’s daughter. Atticus and his family endure all sorts of abuse from white townspeople who are livid with him for representing a black man. When Robinson is convicted by all white jury, even when it becomes clear that he was innocent, he tries to run from jail finally getting himself killed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I think there’s just one kind of folks.  Folks.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;-&lt;em&gt;Scout Finch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The name of the book is also very well-chosen, it represents killing of the innocents. Maudie tells Scout: “Mockingbirds don’t do one thing but make music for us to enjoy. They don’t eat up people’s gardens, don’t nest in corn cribs, they don’t do one thing but sing their hearts out for us. That’s why it’s a sin to kill a mockingbird.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What moves To Kill a Mockingbird to classic status is its morality and ability to draw sympathy out of readers as much today as when it was written in 1960. The book deals with heavy issues of racism, oppression, injustice. Amazingly, it is able to handle these deep and sensitive areas without feeling depressing or preachy. Lee accomplishes this by making the narrator a child and allowing us to learn along with her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/to-kill-a-mockingbird.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/to-kill-a-mockingbird.html</guid>
        
        <category>book</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>to kill a mockingbird</category>
        
        <category>harper lee</category>
        
        <category>finch</category>
        
        
        <category>book review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;margin: 10px; float: left&quot; alt=&quot;Book Cover&quot; src=&quot;http://i2.wp.com/i1326.photobucket.com/albums/u643/BeerSting/Book%20covers/the-catcher-in-the-rye-by-j-d-salinger_zps0ed64285.jpeg&quot; /&gt;
Title: The Catcher in the Rye&lt;br /&gt;
Author: J.D. Salinger&lt;br /&gt;
Publisher: Penguin Books&lt;br /&gt;
ISBN: 9780241950425&lt;br /&gt;
Genre: Classics/Literary Fiction&lt;br /&gt;
Pages: 192&lt;br /&gt;
Source: Personal Copy&lt;br /&gt;
Rating: 5/5  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s one of those book you either love or hate, there’s nothing in between. The novel was included on &lt;a title=&quot;Time (magazine)&quot; href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_(magazine)&quot;&gt;Time&lt;/a&gt;‘s 2005 list of the 100 best English-language novels written since 1923,and it was named by &lt;a title=&quot;Modern Library&quot; href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Modern_Library&quot;&gt;Modern Library&lt;/a&gt; and its readers as one of the &lt;a title=&quot;Modern Library 100 Best Novels&quot; href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Modern_Library_100_Best_Novels&quot;&gt;100 best English-language novels of the 20th century&lt;/a&gt;. It has been frequently challenged in the United States and other countries for its liberal use of profanity and portrayal of sexuality. It also deals with complex issues of identity, belonging, connection, and alienation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Catcher in the Rye is about alienation, the main character Holden Caulfield wants to make connection with other people but almost every scene in the book shows him trying to do that and failing. It’s the story of Caulfield between a short span of him dropping out of Pency Prep to finally deciding to go home. He may come out to seem lazy, stubborn, immature, unfocused, untruthful, dangerously short-sighted and lost in his own world of unrealistic expectations but all that makes him connect better to the teenage mind and it’s this aspect which makes the book still relevant though it was first released in 1951, giving it a place on shelf of timeless books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book is all about the Holden’s dream of being “the catcher in the rye”.  He is so against the concept of growing up and to giving into the pain and sadness that he sees as the result of becoming an adult that he wants nothing more than to spend his life protecting others from losing the innocence of childhood. Just like standing on the edge of some crazy cliff and catching everybody who’s ignorantly going to jump off it not knowing what’s on the other side of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book got into quite a controversies. &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Hinckley,_Jr.&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;John Hinckley Jr.&lt;/a&gt; attempted an assassination on &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ronald_Reagan&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ronald Reagan&lt;/a&gt; in 1981 and one of the books owned by him was the one written by Salinger. &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_David_Chapman&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark David Chapman&lt;/a&gt; shot &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Lennon&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;John Lennon&lt;/a&gt;, Chapman was arrested with his worn personal copy of the book, inside which he had written, “To Holden Caulfield, From Holden Caulfield, This is my statement”. What is it about this book that evokes such reactions, you might think. There’s nothing in the book, it’s all in you. The book just heightens your inner emotions and angst.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/the-catcher-in-the-rye.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/the-catcher-in-the-rye.html</guid>
        
        <category>book</category>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>the catcher in the rye</category>
        
        <category>J.D. Salinger</category>
        
        <category>Holden Caulfield</category>
        
        
        <category>book review</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>At first sight</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Although he wanted to go talk to her, Sushant could not bring himself to interrupt such a beauty. It was not the kind of beauty that lies in the eye of beholder, it was the beauty that glanced by any pair of eyes would look as beautiful. Her well-toned body posture moved childlike yet calmly, talking to her friend and making different hand movements. Her beauty was breathtaking, and so was her lively spirit. Sushant knew that she would be angry at him for gazing bluntly at her without letting her know but his teenage first-year-in-the-college soul didn’t care of any such consequences and continued living the moments. He was not sure if Axl Rose had someone similar to her in his mind when he sang the song ‘Sweet Child O’ Mine’. Her eyes sparkled and reminded him of the bluest sky, vast with beauty and mystery. A slight breeze dazed through her long mane, spreading the sweet cologne in the air. During that moment of visual euphoria, Sushant knew that she was one girl he would never be able to forget. Their eyes got into direct contact. She must have heard me, he thought as she started moving toward him. The sweet smell grew stronger in the dense air as she moved toward him. He never meant to disturb her just to enjoy her beauty. Her lips smiled when she got close enough to him. She moved her head suddenly as to caress his face by her hair and all he could see was her dark jet black hairs all over his face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BAM!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sushant woke up to the smell of cologne the girl was wearing who came and sat next to him in the library, the feeling put a smile on his face, a satisfying happiness overwhelmed all his emotions. The past three hours had been spent in books and boredom induced coma which he preferred over a normal sleep. Night sleep was a rarity as it was his final semester of college and he had to wrap up many stuffs before leaving the college. The only thing that kept him all working and lively was memories of his time spent with Surabhi. It was almost six in the evening and he came back to his room. It was messy and all the stuffs were  at just the most wrong place it could be. He just fell on the bed and reached his hand to the mini fridge beside it for the cold drink. There were no bottles, only thing left were the chocolate cornettos. He took one and started enjoying it. He knew he had to complete the paper on VLSI that very day but he was not into the right mood. The chocolate aroma took over his mood and made him forget everything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why are you not working on your paper?”, asked Surabhi putting on a concerned face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m just not feeling like it.”, was Sushant’s carefree reply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You know that tomorrow’s the last date to submit it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Yeah! but I’ve more than 12 hours in my hand that would be more than enough.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Didn’t you said the same thing last time and fell asleep in the middle and your grade had to suffer because of it.”, was Surabhi’s comeback. She could be a really good lawyer, Sushant thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m a changed person now.”, Sushant replied with a smirk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t have a reason to believe that.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aren’t girls supposed to think by heart than brain, was Sushant’s flow of thought, I guess she’s different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Okay, I’ll be working now but I’m feeling all tired and alone.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I knew you would come up with such excuse so I brought you a box of chocolate ice-cream and I’m here to help you throughout the night.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Okay”, said Sushant with almost no enthusiasm what so ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I won. Let’s work.”, Surabhi exclaimed happily jumping up and down eating her favorite chocolate flavored ice-cream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She won, yeah if she wants to win like this I’ll be more than happy to let her win at every moment of my life, Sushant happily said to himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sushant’s cornetto got over and so did his chocolate aroma induced dream.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2014 17:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/at-first-sight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughtshttp://anuragaryan.github.io/Raw-Thoughts/2014/at-first-sight.html</guid>
        
        <category>love</category>
        
        <category>fiction</category>
        
        <category>guns n' roses</category>
        
        <category>Sushant</category>
        
        <category>Surabhi</category>
        
        
        <category>fiction</category>
        
        <category>story</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
