<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raw Thoughts</title>
    <description>Raw thoughts that keep hovering over Anurag Aryan's head.</description>
    <link>http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 11:11:46 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 11:11:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World.</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;raw-thoughts-blog-number-one&quot;&gt;Raw Thoughts blog number One.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not a writer nor your traditional a post a week blogger. Don’t expect anything from this blog or you’ll be disappointed. This is just going to be the dumping zone for my brain’s musing.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few things I’ve learned in my travels through this crazy college life which is about to end.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One&lt;/strong&gt;, A morning of awkwardness is better than a night of loneliness.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;, You’ve your whole life to make sensible and mature decisions, this is not the time.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three&lt;/strong&gt;, GPA is not important, except during placements, approaching teachers for project, asking class nerds for favors, or to deserve respect from juniors.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Four&lt;/strong&gt;, You’re never going to remember the 8am class in the morning. What you’re going to remember is the 9am screw up you did between the 8am &amp;amp; 10am class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Five&lt;/strong&gt;, Go talk to her asshole, she won’t kill you and anyway at this stage there’ll be no heartbreak that alcohol won’t fix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I wrap this up, I want to ask why is this country of Engineers producing sub-par engineers working in a call centre?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2015 16:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/hello-world.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.comhttp://rawthoughts.anuragaryan.com/2015/hello-world.html</guid>
        
        <category>college, engineers</category>
        
        
        <category>college</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
